printfection.com 2019-02-26

# Printfection Legal Center

Privacy Policy

Printfection, LLC (“ **Printfection** ”, “ **Company** ”) is committed to protecting the privacy of individuals who visit the Company’s Web Sites (“ **Visitors** ”), companies or individuals who register to use the Services as defined below (“ **Customers** ”), and individuals who receive promotional items through our services (“ **Recipients** ”), collectively referred to herein as “ **Users** ”. This Privacy Policy describes Printfection’s privacy practices in relation to the use of the Company’s Web Sites and the related applications and services offered by Printfection (collectively, the “ **Services** ”), as well as individuals’ choices regarding use, access and correction of personal information collected by Printfection as described in this Privacy Policy. 

Websites Covered

Printfection owns and operates certain Web Sites, including [www.printfection.com](https://www.printfection.com/) and others that are affiliated with printfection.com (collectively, the “ **Web Sites** ”). This Privacy Policy covers the information practices, including how the Company collects, uses, shares and secures the personal information you provide, of Web Sites that link to this Privacy Policy, including the Web Sites (also referred to as “ **Printfection’s Web Sites** ”, “ **the Company’s Web Sites** ”). 

Printfection complies with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from European Union and Switzerland to the United States, respectively. Printfection has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/

Types of Information Collected

When you interact with us through the Services or Company’s Web Sites we may collect Personal Data and other information from you, as further described below:

 **Personal Data you Provide through the Printfection Services and Web Sites**. We collect Personal Data from you when you voluntarily provide such information, such as when you contact us with inquiries, order items, redeem giveaway codes for items, register for access to the Printfection Services, or use the Printfection Services and Web Sites. Data collected may include: First Name, Last Name, Email, Birthday, Gender, Location, Address, Company Name, Phone Number, Credit Card Number or other financial information, and other personal information (“ **Personal Data** ”).

 **By voluntarily providing us with Personal Data you are consenting to our use of it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data through the Printfection Services you acknowledge and agree that such Personal Data may be transferred from your current location to the offices and servers of Printfection and the authorized third parties.**

 **Passively Collected Data** : When you interact with the Printfection Services and Web Sites, we and third parties that provide functionality in the Services, may engage, receive, collect and store certain types of information through automatic data collection tools including cookies, pixel tags, web beacons, embedded web links and similar technology. Such information, which is collected passively using various technologies, may include but is not limited to your Internet Protocol (IP) address, information about your device, referring/exit pages and URLs and number of clicks. Printfection may store such information itself or such information may be included in databases owned and maintained by Printfection affiliates, agents or service providers. The Printfection Services may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of Users, the number of Visitors to each page of our Web Sites, and the domain names of our Users’ internet service providers.

In operating the Printfection Services, we may set or access small pieces of data called “cookies”, web beacons or similar technologies on your computer. A cookie is a piece of information that the computer that hosts our Printfection Services gives to your browser when you access the Printfection Services. Our cookies help provide additional functionality to the Printfection Services and help us analyze Web site usage more accurately. For instance, the Printfection Services may set a cookie on your browser that allows you to access the Printfection Services without needing to remember and then enter a password more than once during a visit to a given Printfection Service. Most browsers allow you to block and delete cookies. However, if you block cookies, some portions of our Services may not work properly. The Printfection Services do not respond to Do Not Track signals.

 **Aggregated Data** : The data collected may be anonymized on an aggregated non-proprietary information basis and may be used for any purpose including, but not limited, to analyze and track data, determine popularity of certain services and gain more information about users online activity.

Use of Personal Data

Personal Data is mainly used for Printfection’s own internal purposes in order to provide the Printfection Services to you including but not limited to producing and shipping items, processing orders, customer service issues, maintaining and improving the Web Sites, and providing Printfection marketing materials. If you provide Personal Data for a certain reason, we may use the Personal Data in connection with the reason for which it was provided. For instance, if you contact us by e-mail, we will use the Personal Data you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem. Also, if you provide Personal Data in order to obtain access to the Printfection Services, we will use your Personal Data to provide you with access to such services and to monitor your use of such services. Printfection may also use Personal Data and other personally non-identifiable information to track and analyze the usage and performance of the Web site and Printfection Services. Printfection uses this information internally to assist in determining changes and/or upgrades to the Web Site, whether to add or discontinue specific products or services, and for internal market analysis purposes. Printfection may use this information to contact you in the future to tell you about services or products we believe will be of interest to you or other Printfection Services-related announcements. If we do so, each communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to “opt-out” of receiving future communications. In addition, if at any time you wish not to receive any future communications or you wish to have your name deleted from our mailing lists, please contact us as indicated below. Printfection reserves the right to send you notifications regarding your account even if you opt-out of all voluntary email notifications (such notifications may include order status, account status, or other non-marketing notifications not covered by the opt-out).

We will also provide an EU or Swiss individual with opt-out or opt-in choice before we share their data with third parties other than our agents (our agents include our third-party printing, fulfillment, and/or shipping companies), or before we use it for a purpose other than which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized. 

To limit the use and disclosure of your personal information, please submit a written request to privacy@printfection.com.

Disclosure of Personal Data

In general, we do not disclose Personal Data to third parties without your prior consent. However, we reserve the right to do so in certain limited situations as identified below:

 **Agents, Service Providers**. In the course of providing you the Printfection Services, we may at our option use third party service providers to provide some or all of the Printfection Services you may request in your use of the Services. Example of this include but are not limited to the use of third party vendors to create, store or fulfill the items sold or distributed to you, to host the service at a facility for servers, to send out email updates about Printfection Services, or to process payments by you through the Printfection Services. We make all commercially reasonable efforts to make sure that these third party vendors use your Personal Data only to the extent necessary to provide the Services to you. However, we cannot guarantee that a third party vendor will not disclose your Personal Data.

 **Legal Requirements**. Printfection may disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law, in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements, or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation, (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of Printfection or our customers, (iii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of Users of the Printfection Services or the public, (iv) protect against legal liability or suspected fraud, or (v) investigate, prevent or take action regarding violations of Printfection’s Master Services Agreement, if applicable.

 **Successors in Interest**. We may also disclose your Personal Data to any successor in interest to our company, including, but not limited to any third party company that may acquire or merge with Printfection. In the event of a merger or sale of all or substantially all of the assets of Printfection, your Personal Data will most likely be part of the transaction. 

**Disclosure of Non Personally Identifiable Information**. We may disclose any non personally identifiable information we collect to our strategic business partners, potential business partners, investors, advisors and customers. This information is usually disclosed in terms of aggregate numbers. Since the information cannot be traced back to you directly, you may not “opt-out” of our use of the information.

Under certain circumstances Printfection may remain liable for the acts of Third Parties who perform services on our behalf for their handling of Personal Data that we transfer to them.

Account Deactivation and Deletion

If you no longer desire to use the Printfection Services, you may deactivate your account by sending an email to support@printfection.com. De-activating your account with Printfection may not fully remove the data collected previously as contemplated in this Privacy Policy.

Exclusions

This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide Printfection through the Printfection Services or other means. This includes, but is not limited to, questions, comments, suggestions, ideas, feedback or other information submitted by a Visitor, Recipient, or Customer to Printfection or posted by a Visitor, Recipient, or Customer to any public areas of the Printfection Services, including those that may be integrated into social media providers (e.g. bulletin boards, community web site, Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, etc); any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products; and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, “ **Unsolicited Information** ”). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and Printfection shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute such Unsolicited Information for any purposes, commercial or otherwise, to others without limitation or attribution.

Children

Printfection does not knowingly collect any information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13 please do not submit any Personal Data through the Printfection Services. We will affirmatively delete any information for which we have knowledge came from or pertains to a child under the age of 13. Children between the ages of 13 and 18 may use our Web Site and Services only under a parent or legal guardian’s supervision. If you are a parent or legal guardian of a child between the ages of 13 and 18 and you do not want your child’s Personal Data in our records, or do not wish the child to receive communications from us, please contact us and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.

Security of Personal Data

You use Printfection at your own risk. Printfection employs commercially reasonable technology and systems (including encryption and secure socket layer technology(SSL)) to protect your Personal Data from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. We use other physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the security and confidentiality of the information collected and to prevent unauthorized access to or disclosure of your information.

Other Terms and Conditions

Your access to and use of the Printfection Services is subject to any additional terms applicable to such Printfection Services that may be posted on the Printfection Services from time to time, including without limitation, Printfection’s [Terms of Use](https://legal.printfection.com/#terms-of-use) and [Master Service Agreement](https://legal.printfection.com/#master-service-agreement) available at legal.printfection.com.

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Printfection commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Printfection at privacy@printfection.com.

Printfection has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the Privacy Shield Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers for more information and to file a complaint. 

Finally, as a last resort and in limited situations, EU and Swiss individuals may seek redress from the Privacy Shield Panel, a binding arbitration mechanism. For more information on binding arbitration, see US Department of Commerce's Privacy Shield Framework: Annex I (Binding Arbitration). 

The Federal Trade Commission (FTC) has jurisdiction over Printfection’s compliance with the Privacy Shield.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

The Printfection Services and Printfection’s business may change from time to time. As a result it may be necessary for Printfection to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Printfection reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy in its sole discretion from time to time without prior notice. If the changes are significant, we will, in our sole discretion, post a notice on the homepage of our Web Sites or notify you at the email address we have on file for your account and provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of your continued use of our Services. Printfection strives to provide notifications to Users in a timely manner, it is not responsible for lost or late notifications regarding this Privacy Policy. Please review this policy periodically, and especially before you provide any Personal Data. This Privacy Policy was last updated on the date indicated above. Your continued use of the Printfection Services after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.

Users’ Rights; Contacting Printfection

You have the right to access the Personal Data in our possession that maintain about you and to correct, change or delete your Personal Data if it is not accurate, outdated or has been processed in violation of this Privacy Policy. You also have the right to object to the disclosure of your information to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy, except for disclosures made to agents and service providers, as well as to the use of your information for a purpose that is materially different from the purposes for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by you. An individual (US, EU, Swiss or otherwise) who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data, should direct their query to privacy@printfection.com or by regular mail address below. If requested to remove data, we will respond within a reasonable timeframe.

Please also feel free to contact us if you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the information practices of the Printfection Services.

You may contact us at privacy@printfection.com or by regular mail addressed to:

Printfection LLC  
Customer Service  
3700 Quebec St Unit 100-136  
Denver, CO 80207
